shopgates.com 2002-06-06

# ShopA-Z.com Privacy Policy

ShopA-Z.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our customer's privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the 7,000 websites that comprise the ShopA-Z.com family of websites. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Websites. Your IP address is used to help identify you, your account, and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

"Cookies" are small files containing information that are stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit any of our websites. We also use cookies to track your "click stream" to better understand how our websites are performing which enables us to enhance our websites usability. 

Our website's registration form calls for users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their ZIP code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company, promotional materials, the status of the users order, and for personal special events such as birthdays, upon the users request. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected on our websites. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience across all of ShopA-Z.com's 7,000 websites, showing them content that we feel matches their interests, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis, and at no time will specific personal information be shared.

These websites contain links to other websites not owned and operated by ShopA-Z.com. ShopA-Z.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

Our websites use order forms for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email, billing, and shipping addresses) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers, and to confirm that those orders were shipped and received. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their ZIP code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company, promotional materials, and to inform them of products, and/or services they have won for participating in the survey. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected on our websites. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience across all of ShopA-Z.com's 7,000 websites, showing them content that we feel matches their interests, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis, and at no time will specific personal information be shared.

We run contests in conjunction with our surveys on our websites in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their ZIP code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company, promotional materials, and to inform them of products and/or services they have won for participating in the contest. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected on our websites. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience on our websites, showing them content that we feel matches their interests, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis, and at no time will specific personal information be shared.

**Public Forums**  
The ShopA-Z.com family of websites makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
The ShopA-Z.com family of websites has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Supplementation Information**  
Our websites supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

**Children's Guidelines**  
At ShopA-Z.com we take the security of children seriously and have instituted measures to ensure that security.

ShopA-Z.com will NOT collect online contact information of children under the age of 14 without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent

ShopA-Z.com will NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent

ShopA-Z.com will NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent

ShopA-Z.com will NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent

ShopA-Z.com will NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our websites provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

Our websites give users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

You can send email to:  

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Customer Care  
ShopA-Z.com, Inc.  
5900 La Place Ct. Suite 100  
Carlsbad, CA 92008
